businessenglishpod.com 2019-12-22

# Privacy Policy | Business English Pod :: Learn Business English Online

**Privacy Policy**  
**1\. Introduction**  
This is the Privacy Statement for [Business English Pod Ltd](http://www.businessenglishpod.com/), and the Services provided via the [www.BusinessEnglishPod.com](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/) web site and mobile apps. By accessing the [www.BusinessEnglishPod.com](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/) web site and services, you are agreeing that your usage is subject to this Statement. 

**2\. Definitions**  
**BEP:** Unless specifically stated, BEP shall mean the company Business English Pod Ltd., the owner and operator of [www.BusinessEnglishPod.com](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/).  
  
**Service:** The internet web site [www.BusinessEnglishPod.com](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/), and the online internet services and resources contained on the web site, and any associated service delivery mechanisms.

**Member / Premium Subscriber / Group:** A person or organisation that has paid the required fees and charges to access the Service.

**User/User Log In:** An individual person who has been issued with a unique username and password to access the Service has part of a Subscription. 

**3\. Collection of Personal Information**  
If you simply visit our web site, we do not capture any personal information from you.

We may collect information about your visit, including the pages you view, the links you click and other actions taken in connection with the BEP sites and services. We also collect certain standard information that your browser sends to every website you visit, such as your IP address, browser type and language, access times and referring Web site addresses.

When you receive newsletters or promotional e-mail from BEP, we may use customized links or similar technologies to determine whether the e-mail has been opened and which links you click in order to provide you more focused e-mail communications or other information.

If you are a Premium Subscriber to the BEP Service, we maintain at a minimum the following information:

  * Your Name, User Name and Password
  * Email Address
  * Company/Organisation Name (if applicable)
  * Financial transaction summary (note, we do not collect or store any user credit card information on this site.)

We also sometimes will store copies of correspondence between you and us in your subscription and user record, or elsewhere, to assist us with providing a high level of customer service.

This is the minimum amount of information necessary to properly conduct our subscription systems. We may store other information that you have provided to us in the course of the provision of the BEP Service. 

**4\. Cookies**  
Cookies are small pieces of information stored by web sites on your computer. If you have configured your web browser not to warn about cookies, you probably have quite a few already stored on your hard drive. You must have cookies enabled in your browser in order to use this web site – we use the cookie to track whether you are logged in, and to store your log in details, and these are used to enhance your experience of the site.

For more information, please read our [Cookie Policy page](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/about/privacy-policy/cookie-policy/). 

**5\. Sharing of Your Personal Information**  
Except as described in this statement, we will not disclose your personal information outside of BEP and its controlled subsidiaries and affiliates without your consent.

BEP may hire other companies to provide limited services on our behalf, such as handling the processing and delivery of mailings, providing customer support, hosting websites, processing transactions, or performing analysis of our services. Those companies will be permitted to obtain only the personal information they need to deliver the service. They are required to maintain the confidentiality of the information and are prohibited from using it for any other purpose.

We may access and/or disclose your personal information if we believe such action is necessary to: (a) comply with the law or legal process served on BEP; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of BEP (including the enforcement of our agreements); or (c) act in urgent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of BEP services or members of the public. 

**6\. Accessing Your Personal Information**  
You are able to access and change your user information by logging into the BEP site and Service here:  
<https://businessenglishpod.com/aMember/member>

If you wish to see the entirety of the information in your subscription record, please contact us and we will arrange a copy. If you wish to update or correct any part of the information, please advise us and we will make the changes as quickly as possible. 

**7\. Security of Your Personal Information**  
BEP is committed to protecting the security of your personal information. We use a variety of security technologies and procedures to help protect your personal information from unauthorized access, use, or disclosure. 

It is your responsibility to keep your password confidential. Do not share this information with anyone. If you are sharing a computer with anyone you should always choose to log out before leaving the Service to protect access to your information from subsequent users. 

**8\. Deletion of Old Information**  
If you advise us that you no longer require your premium subscription, our standard procedure is to delete your record from the subscription database, thus destroying the personal information we maintain about you. 

**9\. Credit Card Information**  
Our credit card processing service is provided via PayPal and 2CheckOut. No credit card information is collected or stored by BEP. BEP will not be liable for the management, storage, processing and handling of your personal and credit card information by PayPal or 2CheckOut. 

**10\. Personal Information for Marketing Purposes**  
On occasion BEP conducts marketing campaigns involving email, direct mail letters and other marketing tools, using mailing list databases. If we send you a letter or otherwise contact you, and you decide you do not wish to receive further communication from us, we will remove you from the marketing database.

By establishing a Free Trial or Premium Membership Account you give your consent for BEP to contact you by post, telephone, facsimile, email and other methods for marketing purposes.

Premium Subscribers agree that BEP can disclose their company name and subscription level for promotional purposes. 

**11\. Personal Information for Security Purposes**  
We use Clicky Web Analytics to log and analyze the traffic to our web site. You may review Clicky’s privacy policy [here](https://clicky.com/terms/privacy). We log “personal data” to Clicky as follows, for the stated legitimate purposes. A “Unique ID” tracking cookie to identify unique visitors, your IP address for security and fraud prevention, and your username to help us to analyze visitor behavior and assist with customer service needs. 

**12\. Mandatory Communications**  
We may use your personal information to send certain mandatory service communications such as welcome emails, billing reminders, information on technical service issues, and security announcements. 

**13\. Changing your Personal Information**  
You can review your personal information and make any necessary changes, at any time by logging in to your account at <https://businessenglishpod.com/aMember/member> and changing your preferences by clicking the “Edit Profile” link. 

**14\. Updates**  
We may from time to time update this Privacy Policy, and will post the latest version here on the web site, and endeavour to notify subscribers via email bulletins. 

**15\. Contacting BEP**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the Service or your dealings with BEP, please contact: [editor@BEP.com](mailto:editor@businessenglishpod.com) or see the [Contacts page](https://www.businessenglishpod.com/contact/) for other ways to contact us.

This page was last updated on 15 May 2018.
